The Fetish UP206
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
The Fetish
1948 -- 1968
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Dean of Student Affairs
UP206
0.5 Linear Feet
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains The Fetish. It is a newsletter for commuter students that was published every couple of months. Its former names were the Trav-hiller and the Off-hiller.
- The Fetish, published by the Off-Hill Council, 1948 -- 1968; UP206.001; 0.5 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains issues of The Fetish, a newsletter for commuter students that was published every couple of months. Its former names were the Trav-hiller and the Off-hiller.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Trav-Hiller, 1948-11; UP206.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Trav-Hilller, 1949-03; UP206.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Trav-Hiller, 1949-05; UP206.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Trav-Hiller, 1949-11; UP206.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - The Commuter Newsletter, 1959-04; UP206.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - The Off-Hiller, 1963-10; UP206.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Off-Hiller, 1963-12; UP206.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - The Off-Hiller, 1964-02; UP206.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Off-Hiller4, 1964-05; UP206.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - The Off-Hiller, 1965-04; UP206.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Off-Hiller, 1965-05; UP206.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Off-Hiller, 1966-05; UP206.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - Fetish, 1966-12; UP206.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
  - Fetish, 1967-01; UP206.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
  - The Fetish, 1967-03; UP206.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
  - The Fetish, 1967-06; UP206.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
  - Fetish, 1967-10; UP206.001.001.00017 (Box 1)
  - The Fetish, 1968-04; UP206.001.001.00018 (Box 1)
  - Fetish, 1968-12; UP206.001.001.00019 (Box 1)